{ "questions":[
  {
    "question": "Opposite of RELINQUISH",
    "correct_answer": "Possess",
    "options": [
      "Abdicate",
      "Renounce",
      "Possess",
      "Deny"
    ]
  },  {
    "question": "Read each sentence to find out whether there is any grammatical error in it",
    "correct_answer": "got drowned in the Pacific Ocean",
    "options": [
      "An Indian ship", 
      "laden with merchandise",
"got drowned in the Pacific Ocean",
"No error"
    ]
  },  {
    "question": "Opposite of FRAUDULENT",
    "correct_answer": "Genuine",
    "options": [
    "Candid",
    "Direct",
    "Forthright",
    "Genuine"
    ]
  },  {
    "question": "Read each sentence to find out whether there is any grammatical error in it. The error, if any will be in one part of the sentence. (Ignore the errors of punctuation, if any)",
    "correct_answer": "it is meek and humble",
    "options": [
"According to the Bible",
"it is meek and humble",
"who shall inherit the earth",
"No error"    
    ]
  },  {
    "question": "Find the correctly spelt word",
    "correct_answer": "Chancellery",
    "options": [
      "Chancelary",
      "Chancellery",
      "Chancelery",
      "Chancellary"
    ]
  },  {
    "question": "Find the correctly spelt word",
    "correct_answer": "Veterinary",
    "options": [
      "Vetarinary",
      "Veteninary",
      "Vetinary",
      "Veterinary"
    ]
  },  {
    "question": "The study of ancient societies",
    "correct_answer": "Archaeology",
    "options": [
      "Anthropology",
      "Archaeology",
      "History",
      "Ethnology"
    ]
  },  {
    "question": "A person who speaks many languages",
    "correct_answer": "Polyglot",
    "options": [
      "Linguist",
      "Monolingual",
      "Polyglot",
      "Bilingual"
    ]
  }, {
    "question": "List of the business or subjects to be considered at a meeting",
    "correct_answer": "Agenda",
    "options": [
      "Schedule",
      "Timetable",
      "Agenda",
      "Plan"
    ]
  },  {
    "question": "choose the one which best expresses the given sentence in Passive/Active voice.I remember my sister taking me to the museum.",
    "correct_answer": "I remember being taken to the museum by my sister",
    "options": [
      "I remember I was taken to the museum by my sister",
      "I remember being taken to the museum by my sister",
      "I remember myself being taken to the museum by my sister",
      "I remember taken to the museum by my sister"
    ]
  },  {
    "question": "The waiter hasn't brought the coffee ____ I've been here an hour already.",
    "correct_answer": "yet",
    "options": [
      "till",
      "up",
      "yet",
      "still"
    ]
  }, {
    "question": "There is an incomplete statement followed by fillers is given. Pick out the best one which can complete incomplete stem correctly and meaningfully.  ",
    "correct_answer": "are losing their heads",
    "options": [
      "behave in a socially acceptable manner",
      "exhibit pleasant mannerism",
      "are losing their heads",
      "agree to whatever you say"
    ]
  },  {
    "question": "Catching the earlier train will give us the ____ to do some shopping.",
    "correct_answer": "chance",
    "options": [
      "chance",
      "luck",
      "possibility",
      "occasion"
    ]
  },  {
    "question": "Choose the word which best expresses the meaning of the given word ATTEMPT",
    "correct_answer": "Try",
    "options": [
      "Serve",
      "Explore",
      "Try",
      "Explain"
    ]
  },  {
    "question": "The performance of our players was rather worst than I had expected.  ",
    "correct_answer": "worse than I had expected",
    "options": [
      "bad as I had expected",
      "worse than I had expected",
      "worse than expectation",
      "worst than was expected"
    ]
  },  {
    "question": "If ratio of the areas of two squares is 1:4, the ratio of their perimeters is",
    "correct_answer": "1:2",
    "options": [
      "1:2",
      "1:4",
      "1:6",
      "1:8"
    ]
  },  {
    "question": "A room is 6m long, 5m broad and 4m high. The maximum length of rod that can be kept in the room is",
    "correct_answer": "sqrt(77)",
    "options": [
      "sqrt(61)",
      "sqrt(16)",
      "sqrt(36)",
      "sqrt(77)"
    ]
  },  {
    "question": " 4^61 + 4^62 + 4^63 + 4^64 + 4^65 is divisible by",
    "correct_answer": "11",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "3",
      "5",
      "17"
    ]
  },  {
    "question": " If a*b = 2a+3b, then the value of 2*3 + 3*4 is",
    "correct_answer": "31",
    "options": [
      "24",
      "31",
      "32",
      "34"
    ]
  },  {
    "question": "The average of three numbers is 77. The first number is twice the second and the second number is twice the third. Find the first number.",
    "correct_answer": "132",
    "options": [
      "66",
      "77",
      "33",
      "132"
    ]
  }
]
}
